<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>trmccormick</title>
        <link>https://trmccormick.com/</link>
        <description>trmccormick</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><managingEditor>trevor.ryan.mccormick@gmail.com (Trevor McCormick)</managingEditor>
            <webMaster>trevor.ryan.mccormick@gmail.com (Trevor McCormick)</webMaster><lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Jul 2021 09:08:22 -0400</lastBuildDate>
            <atom:link href="https://trmccormick.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <item>
    <title>Preparing for the AWS Certified Solutions Architect Associate Exam</title>
    <link>https://trmccormick.com/aws_certified_solutions_architect_associate/</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jun 2021 11:20:22 -0400</pubDate><author>trevor.ryan.mccormick@gmail.com (Trevor McCormick)</author><guid>https://trmccormick.com/aws_certified_solutions_architect_associate/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[The AWS Certified Solutions Architect Associate Exam tests your ability to translate specific client needs into basic cloud architectural designs. While the AWS Cerified Cloud Practitioner Exam covers the core concepts of AWS at a broad level, the Solutions Architect Associate Exam goes a level deeper in all areas. You should have hands-on experience designing end-to-end solutions, deploying VPCs that support various networking, compute, storage, and database strategies.
Background There is no better preparation than hands-on experience with AWS.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>How To Query PostgreSQL in AWS RDS with Python</title>
    <link>https://trmccormick.com/aws_rds_postgres_python/</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 11:20:22 -0400</pubDate><author>trevor.ryan.mccormick@gmail.com (Trevor McCormick)</author><guid>https://trmccormick.com/aws_rds_postgres_python/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[In this post I&rsquo;ll walk through:
 how to create a public PostgreSQL instance in RDS using free-tier how to create a table and load it with data from a csv file how to query data from that table using psycopg2  PostgreSQL on RDS The only thing you have to do in the AWS console is create a Postgres DB instance and make sure it is open to the public (just for this example).]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Preparing for the AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner Exam</title>
    <link>https://trmccormick.com/aws_certified_cloud_practitioner/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 04 Oct 2020 19:08:22 -0400</pubDate><author>trevor.ryan.mccormick@gmail.com (Trevor McCormick)</author><guid>https://trmccormick.com/aws_certified_cloud_practitioner/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[The AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner Exam challenges your knowledge of introductory cloud concepts. The exam does not cover any programming, any system admin types of tasks, or any advanced solution architecture designs. Rather, it tests your understanding of the mechanics, the scope, and the benefits of cloud computing, as well as the AWS philosophy in general.
Computing Foundations I recommend browsing through these two courses to evaluate your knowledge of how computers work, from doing basic tasks to coordinating and executing complex operations with other machines.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Build a Serverless Hugo Blog on AWS for $0.50 per month</title>
    <link>https://trmccormick.com/build_hugo_on_aws/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2020 11:20:22 -0400</pubDate><author>trevor.ryan.mccormick@gmail.com (Trevor McCormick)</author><guid>https://trmccormick.com/build_hugo_on_aws/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[This post assumes you already have some familiarity with Hugo for building a blog, and you have set up a free-tier AWS account. You don&rsquo;t have to be an expert at either Hugo or AWS to follow along with the guide below. Really the only requirement is that you&rsquo;re able to follow the Hugo quick start guide.
Below is an AWS architecture diagram I created using diagrams.net, the free version of draw.]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
